In the previous material we have created our awesome book Marklet so we see it divide by categories.
We can inject this code, we can display all the links.
So, for example, if I'm on the page I can go to like VMWF and then on the open book Marklet.
So this is like a Wolfram cloud, I'll use the coloring discovery and display all the links.
And this is how it was actually extracted. Nice.
Obviously we can get another function out, but we see that it's open up
just by a new tab without an extension.
Because for example now I like it, I'm using it in Gopher, but we can have all of it at once.
Alright, and so show me the channels.
I was collecting useful websites for all social media accounts, I'm stirring in a CDM.
So if I want to have like a good, no, say if I want to implement it, have like a full extension,
I'll do it, but I will not record everything because it will take a lot of time and just repeat it if that's because I have to escape it.
But so this is the way we can do. Basically we collect all of the information about social media.
We see the script, we see the channels, those and then we try to understand how it works and then implement it as another tool.
But the very fix what I'm going to do because as we can see if I hover I have a default
Chrome extension when I hover it and one, but we have below.
So this is the first and this is the second.
Obviously that image can be pasted, so if I pass in a new agent, we have two hover tooltips.
But I need only one Chrome with dark background color.
Let me move that original background tooltips file to prevent double display.
So this agent will remove that feature, so we use for the first and action image.
I'll open a new agent now and what I'm going to do, I will create a first script because obviously I will use that huge library that I pre-pert,
but I will not record that.
I'll use a new tap extension as you can see, this is a Discord lookup.
It shows like some styles, invite resolver, GitHub, as I can fully resource basically there.
And what I'm going to do because it has been a lot of that, I can name it as a Discord.
So I want to get a Snowflake ID for Discord directly in Book Marker at under social media directory.
So now I'll just use it, I will just move to auto mode and I will just enter.
So this we walk like a new chat, remember that each actually display, so if the context menu is just a big,
and then all the answers will be worse, so the first answer is usually like the best, so as further it goes, it goes worse, it gets worse, it gets worse.
So it's good to create a new agent and add them.
So it's creating a Snowflake extractor Book Marker, you extract some flags from your special content, convert to timestamps.
So creating a new tab for that.
Alright, it has added a new entry, Book Marker, let's Json, so this is the new Discord Snowflake ID extractor.
So now if I go back, I'll open a Chrome extension manage, I will here, I will just add it again.
As you can see, now in social media there will be probably a Discord Snowflake ID.
So it's from page content and data attributes.
Okay, so it's removed to people but the normal one, but it's okay, we can keep it.
And data attributes the code attempts and display in the model, so we have to go to Discord.
And when I'm in any panel here, and I will go to social media and type Discord, as you can see, we see all of the information.
I'm probably going to adjust, but this way you can actually extract, it actually takes a lot of things here.
Another data, the demand you can easily move it, you can copy the Snowflake and the comments from the channel.
I'm now in Pinocchio Kool-ai Project, so this way we can create our own actually tools based on the functionality that we can use.